[Music]
having a commercial vehicle insurance
lead but don't know how to proceed with
the purchase of a commercial vehicle
insurance policy but wait do you know
that rather than going for offline
purchase of commercial vehicle policy
you can go for online purchase too there
are so many benefits associated with it
and it's more convenient too let me tell
you what all you get with an online
commercial vehicle policy you can choose
the best commercial vehicle insurance
plans from india's 15 plus leading
insurers and not only that you will get
the best premium prices these benefits
also include inspection waivers
along with this payments would be
released timely as well as real-time
reconciliation of your account is done
automatically and also the portal has
easy mmv make model variant selection
process moreover the step-by-step guide
is available in two languages hindi and
english see so many advantages just with
an online purchase of commercial vehicle
policy then why to go for the offline
option find this amazing now come let us
guide you with three simple steps to buy
a commercial vehicle policy online first
fill your name and mobile number here
in the next step you need to select the
type of your vehicle and then vehicles
manufacturer
now select your vehicle's model and
variant and click on view free codes
after this select your vehicle's
registration year and enter the
registration rto of your vehicle proceed
further by clicking on view free codes
here you need to update your policy
expiry date to check the codes select
the option regarding your existing
policies claim
[Music]
you can also modify idv that has ensured
declared value and registration date as
per your requirement select add-on
covers and accessories you want to add
and get appropriate code for your
vehicle
here is your court list ready for you
next you need to fill up the vehicle
details and complete proposal page like
this
[Music]
then click on view summary
you can see the payment details listed
in front of you now you need to select i
confirm that my vehicle has a valid puc
certificate and click on proceed to
payment
select your payment options
and there you go you have finally bought
the commercial vehicle policy with such
simple steps and ease
[Music]